A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2010-2013
The Library of Virginia
51157
xx cubic feet (xx Boxes)
Virginia Secretary of the Commonwealth
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Restricted documents have been sealed within the collection.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Virginia Secretary of Administration on January 23, 2014.
Historical Information
xx
xx
xx
Scope and Content
Secretary of the Commonwealth records, 2010-2013, consist of xx archival boxes and are divided into x series. Series have been designated for These records document the work of the Secretary of the Commonwealth during the McDonnell administration and were created or collected, 2010-2013, though some documents in this collection pre-date this time period.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence, 2010-2013
Series II. Invitations, 2010-2014
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence, 2010-2013., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 1-4)
  This series is housed in 4 boxes and is arranged chronologically. The majority of the correspondence is comprised of correspondence received by the Secretary of the Commonwealth.
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 May. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 June. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 July. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2010 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2010. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011 July. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Received, 201 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2011. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2011. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 May. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 June. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 July. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2012. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2012 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2012 May. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2012 June. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2012 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2012 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2012 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 May. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 June. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 July. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Received, 2013 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Sent, 2013. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - General Assembly, 2013. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - House of Delegates, 2013 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Series II. Invitations, 2010-2014., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 5-7)
  Invitations, 2010-2014, are housed in 3 boxes and are arranged chronologically.
  - Invitations, 2010 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 2010 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 2010 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 2010 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 2010 May. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 2010 June. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 2010 July. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 2010 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 2010 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, 2010 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Invitations, 2010 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, 2010 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Invitations, 2011 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Invitations, 2011 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, 2011 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, 2011 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Invitations, 2011 May. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 2011June-Aug. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 2011 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 2011 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 2011 Nov. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 2011 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 2012 Jan. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 2012 Feb. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 2012 Mar. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, 2012 Apr. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Invitations, 2012 May. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, 2012 June. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Invitations, 2012 July. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Invitations, 2012 Aug. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, 2012 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, 2012 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Invitations, 2012 Nov. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Invitations, 2012 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Invitations, 2013 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 2013 Feb. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 2013 Mar. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 2013 Apr. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 2013 May. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 2013 June. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 2013 July. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 2013 Aug. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 2013 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, 2013 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Invitations, 2013 Nov. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, 2013 Dec. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Invitations, 2014 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Series III. Executive orders and directives, 2010-2013., Extent: 1 box. (Box 8)
  Executive orders and directives, 2010-2013, are housed in 1 box and are arranged by order or directive number.
  - Executive orders (1-8), 2010. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Executive orders (9-20), 2010. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Executive orders (21-30), 2010. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Executive orders (31-43), 2011. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Executive orders (44-57), 2012. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Executive orders (58-68), 2013. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Directives, 2010-2013. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Series IV. Proclamations, 2010-2013., Extent: 1 box. (Box 9)
  Proclamations, 2010-2013, are housed in 1 box and are arranged chronologically. There are only five proclamations in this series.
  - Virginia Day of Prayer, 2010 May 6. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Tech Remembrance Day, 2010 Apr 16. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Rescue Squad and Emergency Medical Services Week, 2010 May 16-22. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Day, 2010 May 31. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - A Day of Service, 2013 Sept 15-29. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Series V. Special project and subject files, 2010-2013., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 10-12)
  Special event and subject files, 2010-2013, are housed in 3 boxes and are arranged alphabetically.
  - Absolute pardons granted, 1966-2005. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cabinet meeting agendas, 2011 Dec-2013. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cabinet retreat, 2012. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Swearing-in, 2010 jan 24. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Seal rules, 2011. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - China Alliance International Holding Group (MOU), 2011. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Decision tracking sheets, 2010 June-Dec. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Decision tracking sheets, 2011 Jan-May. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Electoral College, 2012 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Electoral College - Electors for President and Vice President (Official results), 2012. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Emerging Leaders Program (Sorenson Institute for Political Leadership), 2012. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Events, 2012. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Events, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Financial statements (Support Services), 2010 June-Nov. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Financial statements (Support Services), 2011-2013. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - First House: Two Centuries with Virginia's First Families, 2012 Oct 11. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - George Mason University Social Enterprise graduating class, 2012 July 26. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Governor's Cabinet Exercise, 2010. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Governor's Decision Requests, 2013. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Governor's license plates, 2010. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Governor's proposed amendments to the 2010-2012 Budget - Briefing, 2010 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Govenor's propsed amendemnts to the 2012-2014 Budget - Briefing, 2012 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Kairos Prison Minitry, 2012. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - LEAD VA - Board of Directors Information Notebook, 2010. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - LEAD VA - Board of Directors meeting, 2010 Apr. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Legislative session, 2011. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - LG Electronics (MOU), 2011. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - National Association of Secretaries of State, 2010-2011. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Opinions, 2011-2012. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Procedures, 2010-2011. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Social Entrepreneurship, 2011-2012. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - State of Region (Hampton Roads), 2012. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - State of the Union response, 2010. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Technology contracts, 2012. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Technology upgrades, 2010. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Veterans / Voting, undated. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Video consent forms, 2013. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - VA Adopts: Campaign for 1000 - Kick-off event briefing, 2013 May 17. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - VA Adopts: Campaign for 1000 - Meeting materials, 2013. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - VA Adopts: Campaign for 1000 - Plan, 2013. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - VA Adopts: Campaign for 1000 - Press release and remarks, 2013 May. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Code Commission, 2013. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts, 2012. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Disaster Relief Fund, 2011-2012. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Information Technologies Agency (MOU), 2012. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 2012. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Water Missions International, undated. (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Series VI. Weekly reports, 2010-2011., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 13-15)
  Weekly reports, 2010-2011, are housed in 3 boxes and are arranged chronologically.
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Feb 1. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Feb 10. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Feb 17. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 Feb 19. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Feb 24. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 Feb 26. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Mar 3. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 Mar 5. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Mar 10. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 Mar 11. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Mar 17. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 Mar 19. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Mar 24. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Mar 31. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Apr 7. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 Apr 9. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Apr 14. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Apr 21. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 Apr 23. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Apr 28. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 May 5. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 May 7. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 May 12. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 May 14. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 May 19. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Weekly reports - Cabinet, 2010 May 21. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 May 26. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 June 2. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 June 9. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 June 17. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 June 23. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 June 30. (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 July 7. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 July 21. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 July 28. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Aug 11. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Aug 18. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Aug 25. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Sept 1. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Sept 8. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Sept 22. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Sept 29. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Oct 6. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Oct 13. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Oct 20. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Oct 27. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Nov 3. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Nov 10. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Nov 17. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Dec 1. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Dec 8. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Weekly reports, 2010 Dec 15. (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Jan 5. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Jan 12. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Jan 19. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Jan 26. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Feb 2. (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Feb 9. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Feb 16. (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Feb 23. (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Mar 3. (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Mar 9. (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Mar 16. (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Mar 23. (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Weekly reports, 2011 Mar 30. (Box 14, Folder 34)